blingjewelry.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy – Bling Jewelry

Bling Jewelry Inc. Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.blingjewelry.com (the “Site”). 

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

    \- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

    \- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.  
    \- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.” We do not store or save your credit card numbers or information.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
Communicate with you;  
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING  
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by opting out directly with our advertising partners, which include:  
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads  
CRITEO - https://www.criteo.com/privacy/

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  http://optout.aboutads.info/.

Promotional Marketing & Canadian Anti-Spam laws.  
Subscribing to our newsletter means consenting to be contacted by Bling Jewelry via email or social media. In other words—if you want to hear from us, we will definitely stay in touch! From time to time, you may find Bling Jewelry promotions and special offers in the mail or through email. You are free to opt out of our mailing list at any time if you don’t want these communications. And for the record, BlingJewelry.com will never sell, lease, or rent your email address without permission.

Changing Your Subscription Preferences  
As a registered user, you can log in to change the preferences to (or to not) receive communications. If you don’t want to be contacted about Bling promotions and special offers, select the option and we will respect your wishes.

If you really don’t want to hear from us, you can stop the newsletters and other info by following the ‘unsubscribe’ link in our emails. However, Bling Jewelry may continue to use your personal information to contact you to service your account or as otherwise authorized by law. If you have communicated with us using more than one name or email address, you may still get our emails until these accounts are associated with an opt-out request.

CHECKOUT PARTNERS

BlingJewelry.com partners with PayPal to allow for a safe, secure, and speedy checkout process. International customers should use PayPal as the faster way to get orders processed. Shipping and billing address must match the address on the PayPal account. Read PayPal’s privacy policy here.

BlingJewelry.com partners with Amazon Payments to allow for a safe, secure, and speedy checkout process. If you have an Amazon USA account you can now pay with your Amazon Account. Read Amazon Payments’ Privacy Policy [here](https://payments.amazon.com/sdui/sdui/about?nodeId=82974).

DO NOT TRACK  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS  
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe.

DATA RETENTION  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at contact@blingjewelry.com or by mail using the details provided below:

5901 West Side Avenue, Suite 401, North Bergen, NJ 07047
